cjr.org 2016-06-20

# Privacy Policy - Columbia Journalism Review

### About Us

Mission Statement   
Masthead   
Major Funders   
Press Room   
Follow Us   
Privacy Policy   

* * *

**Privacy Policy**

CJR is committed to protecting your privacy. We do not currently collect personally identifiable information, except in specific instances, such as signing up for our e-mail list. 

Like most websites, CJR does collect non-personal information, such as IP addresses of visitors and data about the usage of pages. This information is used to help us evaluate and improve the site, and understand what our readers are looking for when they visit CJR. We may also disclose aggregated non-personal information to third parties for marketing purposes.

* * *

**Comments Policy**

We ask our readers to express opinions in a manner respectful to the readers and writers of CJR. Criticism of ideas is strongly encouraged, but personal, ad hominem attacks will result in deletion of posted comments and, potentially, banning of the individual user. CJR reserves the right to edit or delete, for reasons of content, comments submitted to CJR. 

* * *

**Commenting Rules**  

CJR reserves the right to edit or delete your comment posting if you, or anyone using your account, violates one of these rules: 

Comments that do not provide a valid e-mail address at which the user associated with it receives e-mail; 

Comments that violate local, state, or federal laws, promote commercial products or services, impersonate another person or entity, or solicit or encourage illegal activity; 

Comments that libel or defame any other individual or party; 

Comments that are abusive, that threaten or harass another individual, are overly antagonistic, deliberately inflammatory, or ad hominem in nature. 

Comments that contain excessive punctuation or capitalization designed solely to pump up the volume of a post. 

Comments which CJR and parties contracted by CJR deem to be otherwise objectionable, inappropriate, off-topic, or offensive. 

* * *

**Permanent Removal**  

CJR reserves the right to remove users / commenters permanently for any of the following: 

Violating any of the rules above more than once. 

Using non-working, outdated e-mail addresses in one’s account. 

Using language CJR deems to be offensive or obscene in one’s username. 

Using multiple accounts to post comments. 

* * *

**Full Legal Disclosure**  

By using the comments feature on CJR or otherwise using this site, you agree that you will not post or otherwise distribute any content that is offensive, obscene, defamatory, unlawful, threatening, abusive, harassing, or deceptive. You also agree that you will not impersonate any other person, and that you will not display or distribute copyrighted material without the express permission of the copyright owner (except as otherwise allowed by law), or infringe any patent, trademark, or other proprietary right of any person. 

To the extent that users express points of view about a political candidate or any other matter, the views expressed are solely those of the user. 

We have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick’s privacy policy at <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>.
